A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, SG 1.27 (A2001) FA488
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, SG 1.27 (A2001)
1970-2001
1991-2000
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller Foundation
FA488
81.22 Cubic Feet 62 standard record storage boxes,
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Project files transferred to the RAC by Rockefeller Foundation, 2001.
Conditions Governing Access
Records more than 10 years old are open for research with select materials restricted as noted. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC. Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. To request an access surrogate be made, or if you are unsure if there is an access surrogate, please contact an archivist.
Arrangement
Reccords are primarily arranged by Accession and the further arranged by Program.
Some subgroups may contain portions of the material that are arranged by the Rockefeller Foundation traditional series (country code) and subseries (program letter) structure.
Records are arranged as received. Within folders, materials are primarily arranged in reverse chronological order.
Separated Materials
Special Formats (digital media) have been separated from the body of the collection. All pertinent items are assigned a unique separation number, as noted. Requests to access open special formats should reference the unique separation number.
Scope and Contents
Contains grant administration records.
- AC.2001.003: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1990-2000; AC.2001.003; 6.55 Cubic Feet 5 record storage boxes
  - Fellowships (F), AC.2001.003.1; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - F-AS-CHINA - Xu Ping, 1992-1996 (Box R3379)
    - F-AS-CHINA - Xuyao, 1992-1996 (Box R3379)
    - F-AS-CHINA - Yan Yitang, 1990-1996 (Box R3379)
    - F-AS-CHINA - Yan Hong, 1992-1995 (Box R3379)
    - F-AS-CHINA - Yang Guanpin, 1992-1995 (Box R3379)
    - F-AS-CHINA - Yin Yanhai, 1990-1998 (Box R3379)
    - F-AS-CHINA - Zhan Xiaoyan, 1992-1996 (Box R3379)
    - F-AS-USA - Zenger, Elizabeth Ann, 1992-1995 (Box R3379)
    - F-AS-CHINA - Zhang Qiang, 1990-1997 (Box R3379)
    - RF 90032 A 54 - Zheng Kangle, 1990-1995 (Box R3379)
  - International Security (IS), AC.2001.003.2; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - IS 9603 - Search for Common Ground - BC Conference: Iranian-American Consultative Group (Not Held), 1995-1998 (Box R3380)
  - Arts and Humanities (AH), AC.2001.003.3; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - AH 9539 - University of Guadalajara (Mexico) - BC Conference: Second International Book Fair Directors, 1995-1997 (Box R3380)
  - Bellagio Conference and Study Center, 120; 5.24 Cubic Feet 4 record storage boxes
    - 120 - CONFERENCE: AIDS CONSULTATION, 1995-1996 (Box R3380)
    - 120 - AIDS VACCINE INITIATIVE - CONFERENCE, 1993-1994 (Box R3380)
    - 120 - AIDS VACCINE INITIATIVE - CONFERENCE - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1993-1994 (Box R3380)
    - 120 - ACCESS TO ARCHIVES- CONFERENCE, 1992-1994 (Box R3380)
    - 120 - AFRICAN WOMEN EDUCATION MINISTERS ? CONFERENCE, 1993-1994 (Box R3380)
    - 120 - CONFERENCE: AID EFFECTIVENESS IN AFRICA, 1994-1995 (Box R3380)
    - 120 - APPROPRIATING GENDER: WOMEN'S ACTIVISM AND THE POLITICIZATION OF RELIGION IN SOUTH ASIA - CONFERENCE, 1993-1995 (Box R3380)
    - 120 - CONFERENCE: ASSESSING THE PAST FOR THE FUTURE: FAMILY PLANNING POLICY PROGRAMS AND RESOURCES, 1996-1997 (Box R3380)
    - 120 - CONFERENCE: ASSESSMENT OF GOALS AND SYSTEMS FOR INTERNATIONAL COOPERATION IN SCIENCE, ENGINEERING AND MEDICINE, 1994-1996 (Box R3380)
    - 120 - AVOIDING NUCLEAR WAR IN SOUTH ASIA - CONFERENCE, 1993-1998 (Box R3380)
    - 120 - CONFERENCE: BIOTECHNOLOGICAL CHALLENGES FOR LAW AND ETHICS, 1994-1997 (Box R3380)
    - 120 - CONFERENCE: CIVILIZATION AND ITS ENDURING DISCONTENTS, 1995-1997 (Box R3381)
    - 120 - CONFERENCE: CRITERIA FOR A WORLD CLASS EDUCATION, 1995-2000 (Box R3381)
    - 120 - DEVELOPMENT IN THE DIGITAL VILLAGE - CONFERENCE, 1994 (Box R3381)
    - 120 - CONFERENCE: EFFECTIVENESS IN ADOLESCENT HEALTH, 1994-1995 (Box R3381)
    - 120 - EMIGRATION DYNAMICS IN DEVELOPING COUNTRIES: MIDTERM REVIEW OF A MAJOR RESEARCH PROJECT - CONFERENCE, 1993-1994 (Box R3381)
    - 120 - EXTRADITION AND HUMAN RIGHTS - CONFERENCE 1994, 1993-1994 (Box R3381)
    - 120 - CONFERENCE: EXTRADITION AND HUMAN RIGHTS, 1994-1996 (Box R3381)
    - 120 - FOLLOW-UP DONOR CONSULTATION ON AGENDA 21 RESEARCH AND CAPACITY BUILDING INITIATIVES - CONFERENCE, 1994 (Box R3381)
    - 120 - GETTING AGRICULTURE MOVING IN THE 1990s - CONFERENCE, 1993-1996 (Box R3381)
    - 120 - CONFERENCE: "GIACOMO PUCCINI: FROM EDGAR TO LA BOHEME" (NOT HELD), 1994-2000 (Box R3381)
    - 120 - GLOBAL AND COMPARATIVE ANALYSIS OF FINANCIAL INSTITUTIONS - CONFERENCE, 1993-1994 (Box R3381)
    - 120 - CONFERENCE: GLOBAL INVESTING FOR THE 21ST CENTURY, 1995-1996 (Box R3381)
    - 120 - GLOBALIZATION OF WORK - CONFERENCE (NOT HELD), 1992-1993 (Box R3381)
    - 120 - GLOBAL SOCIETY AND THE LATINO COMMUNITY - CONFERENCE, 1994-1997 (Box R3381)
    - 120 - CONFERENCE: GULF 2000, 1994-1995 (Box R3381)
    - 120 - CONFERENCE: HEALTH-DEVELOPMENT LINK, 1995-2000 (Box R3381)
    - 120 - CONFERENCE: HILTON HUMANITARIAN PRIZE, 1995-1997 (Box R3381)
    - 120 - CONFERENCE: HOMELAND AND DIASPORA: THE JEWISH PRESENCE IN TWENTIETH CENTURY EGYPT (NOT HELD), 1996 (Box R3381)
    - 120 - CONFERENCE: HUMANITIES AND THE SOCIAL SCIENCES, 1994-1997 (Box R3382)
    - 120 - CONFERENCE: IMPROVING THE PROSPECTS FOR FUTURE PEACE OPERATIONS, 1994-1995 (Box R3382)
    - 120 - INTERNATIONAL ADVOCACY ON WOMEN'S HEALTH-CONFERENCE, 1993-1994 (Box R3382)
    - 120 - CONFERENCE: INTERNATIONAL STUDY OF THE OUTCOMES OF HOSPITAL WORKFORCE RESTRUCTURING, 1995-1998 (Box R3382)
    - 120 - CONFERENCE: LACTATIONAL AMENORRHEA METHOD OF FAMILY PLANNING, 1994-1996 (Box R3382)
    - 120 - CONFERENCE: LEGAL STATUS OF STREET VENDORS IN CITIES, 1994-1996 (Box R3382)
    - 120 - CONFERENCE: MONARCH BUTTERFLY (NOT HELD), 1996 (Box R3382)
    - 120 - CONFERENCE: MUSLIM IMAGES, MUSLIM REALITIES IN THE AMERICAN MEDIA, 1995-1996 (Box R3382)
    - 120 - NATIONAL MINORITIES, NATIONALIZING STATES AND EXTERNAL NATIONAL HOMELANDS IN THE NEW EUROPE - CONFERENCE, 1993-1995 (Box R3382)
    - 120 - CONFERENCE: ORIGIN OF DIPLOMACY, 1995-2000 (Box R3382)
    - 120 - CONFERENCE: PARASITES AND PREGNANCY (NOT HELD), 1995-1997 (Box R3382)
    - 120 - POPULATION FORUM II - CONFERENCE, 1994 (Box R3383)
    - 120 - CONFERENCE: PRESERVATION AND USE OF PALEOANTHROPOLOGICAL RESOURCES IN TANZANIA, 1993-1997 (Box R3383)
    - 120 - CONFERENCE: PROMOTING INTERNATIONAL COOPERATION AMONG MEDICAL JOURNAL EDITORS, 1993-2000 (Box R3383)
    - 120 - PUBLIC HEALTH TRAINING PROGRAMS FOR THE CENTURY - CONFERENCE, 1993-1997 (Box R3383)
    - 120 - CONFERENCE: RESPONDING TO TOBACCO: A DONOR CONSULTATION, 1994-1995 (Box R3383)
    - 120 - CONFERENCE: REMOTE SENSING IN GEOPHYSICS USING DOPPLER TECHNIQUES, 1994-2000 (Box R3383)
    - 120 - ROLE OF RELIGION IN CONFLICT RESOLUTION - CONFERENCE, 1994 (Box R3383)
    - 120 - CONFERENCE: RUSSIA'S DEMOGRAPHIC CRISIS IN COMPARATIVE PERSPECTIVE (NOT HELD), 1995-1996 (Box R3383)
    - 120 - CONFERENCE: SAFE MOTHERHOOD, 1997 (Box R3383)
    - 120 - CONFERENCE: SEA-DUMPED CHEMICAL MUNITION, 1994-2000 (Box R3383)
    - 120 - CONFERENCE: SECURING BODILY INTEGRITY FOR THE SOCIALLY DISADVANTAGED, 1994-1996 (Box R3383)
    - 120 - CONFERENCE: TEACHING OF VALUES THROUGH EDUCATION, MEDIA AND ARTS, 1993-1995 (Box R3383)
    - 120 - THERAPY FOR MALARIA - CONFERENCE, 1993-1995 (Box R3383)
    - 120 - CONFERENCE: UNITED NATIONS POPULATION FUND: SPECIAL ADVISORY GROUP, 1995-1996 (Box R3383)
    - 120 - CONFERENCE: WHITEFLIES AND VIRUSES: MENACE TO WORLD AGRICULTURE, 1995-1996 (Box R3383)
- AC.2001.010: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1992-2000; AC.2001.010; 10.48 Cubic Feet 8 record storage boxes
  - Bellagio Conference and Study Center, 120; 10.48 Cubic Feet 8 record storage boxes
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (ABDUAZJZOV, A.), 1994-1996 (Box R3384)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS {ACHOLONU, C.), 1995-1997 (Box R3384)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS {ADAIR, M.), 1992-1997 (Box R3384)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (ADAMS, D.), 1993-1995 (Box R3384)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (ADNAN, M.), 1994-1996 (Box R3384)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (AGA-ROSSI, E.), 1995-1997 (Box R3384)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (AGOVI, K.), 1992-1994 (Box R3384)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (AKALAITIS, J.), 1995-1996 (Box R3384)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (AMBARTZUMIAN, R.), 1994-1995 (Box R3384)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (ANAYA, S.), 1993-1996 (Box R3384)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (ANDERSON, T.), 1993-1997 (Box R3384)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (ANDREWS, G.), 1992-1995 (Box R3384)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (APPLEBEE, A.), 1993-1996 (Box R3384)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (ARELLANO-CARANDANG, M.), 1993-1997 (Box R3384)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (ARENZ, T.), 1995-1997 (Box R3384)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (ARIDJIS, H.), 1992-1995 (Box R3384)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (ARKOUN, M.), 1994-1996 (Box R3384)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (ARNON, R.), 1993-1996 (Box R3384)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (ARTERBERRY, M.), 1994-1997 (Box R3384)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (ASHOKAMITRAN, T.), 1993-1996 (Box R3384)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (AYALON, D.), 1995-1998 (Box R3384)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (AYALON, O.), 1995-1997 (Box R3384)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (BAKER, C.), 1994-1995 (Box R3384)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (BAL, M.), 1993-1996 (Box R3384)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (BANFIELD, A.), 1993-2000 (Box R3384)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (BARAM, A.), 1994-1995 (Box R3384)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (BARBOSA, A.), 1994-1995 (Box R3384)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (BAKER, WENDY), 1993-1995 (Box R3385)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (BEARDSLEE, WILLIAM R.), 1994-1996 (Box R3385)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (BEEMAN, RICHARD R.), 1995-1996 (Box R3385)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (BEGLARIAN, EVE) (CO-RESIDENT: SUPOVE, KATHLEEN), 1994-1996 (Box R3385)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (BEISER, MORTON), 1994-1996 (Box R3385)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (BENJAMIN, GERALD) (CO-RESIDENT: NATHAN, RICHARD P.), 1995-1996 (Box R3385)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (BEPPU, KEIKO), 1994-2000 (Box R3385)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (BERL, CHRISTINE) (DID NOT GO), 1993-1995 (Box R3385)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (BEYENBACH, KLAUS WERNER), 1994-1996 (Box R3385)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (BHALLA, ALOK), 1995-1997 (Box R3385)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (BIALOBRODA, ANN) (CO-RESIDENT: SCHLESINGER, MARK), 1995-1997 (Box R3385)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (BING, DAVID H.) (CO-RESIDENT: BING, CLAUDINE), 1995-1997 (Box R3385)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (BLUMROSEN, ALFRED W.) (CO-RESIDENT: BLUMROSEN, RUTH GERBER), 1994-1995 (Box R3385)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (BOENINGER, EDGARDO KAUSEL), 1993-1994 (Box R3385)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (BOMBARDIER, CLAIRE) (CO-RESIDENT: WRIGHT, JAMES GARDNER), 1995-1996 (Box R3385)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (BORGMAN, CHRISTINE L.), 1993-1995 (Box R3385)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (BORNEMAN, JOHN W.), 1993-1998 (Box R3385)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (BOUCHARD, LINDA), 1994-1996 (Box R3385)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (BOWLER, PETER JOHN), 1993-1995 (Box R3385)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (BOYD, JEAN), 1994-2000 (Box R3385)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (BREZNAY, JOZSEF), 1994-1996 (Box R3385)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (BROUWER, MARGARET}, 1993-1996 (Box R3385)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (BROWN, WAYNE), 1992-1994 (Box R3385)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (BROWNSTEIN, RACHEL), 1996 (Box R3385)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (BUCHANAN, CONSTANCE HALL}, 1993-1996 (Box R3385)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (BUDENZ, JULIA), 1995-1996 (Box R3385)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (CAMPBELL, DONALD E.) (CO-RESIDENT: KELLY, JERRY S.), 1994-1996 (Box R3385)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (CARLSON, CYNTHIA), 1993-1995 (Box R3385)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (CARPELAN, BO), 1993-1994 (Box R3385)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (CARR, JANET HOWARD)(CO-RESIDENT: SHEPHERD, ROBERTA BARKWORTH), 1993-1995 (Box R3386)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (CARRINGTON, PAUL DEWITT), 1993-1994 (Box R3386)
    - SCHOLARS (CARSON, ANNE), 1994-1996 (Box R3386)
    - SCHOLARS (CARTER, FRANK W.), 1994-1995 (Box R3386)
    - SCHOLARS (CASPER, LEONARD), 1993-1995 (Box R3386)
    - SCHOLARS (CASSELL, JOAN), 1995-1998 (Box R3386)
    - SCHOLARS (CAWS, MARY ANN), 1993-1996 (Box R3386)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (CELLI, JOSEPH)(CO-RESIDENT: KIM, JIN HI), 1994-1997 (Box R3386)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (CHADWICK, SIR HENRY), 1993-1999 (Box R3386)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (CHANDLER, DAVID P.), 1995-1996 (Box R3386)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (CHEN, LINCOLN CHIH-HO), 1993-1994 (Box R3386)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (CHEN, MARTHA ALTER), 1993-1994 (Box R3386)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (CHYLINSKA, BOZENNA), 1995-1996 (Box R3386)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (CLAY, ALLYSON), 1995-1996 (Box R3386)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (COGAN, ROBERT), 1994-1999 (Box R3386)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (COHEN DABAH, ESTHER ), 1995-1997 (Box R3386)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (COHEN, DAVID WILLIAM), 1995-1996 (Box R3386)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (COHEN, STANLEY), 1993-1995 (Box R3386)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (COHEN-SOLAL, ANNIE L.), 1992-1995 (Box R3386)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (COLE, LEONARD A.), 1993-1996 (Box R3386)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (COLISH, MARCIA L.), 1993-1998 (Box R3386)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (COSENTINO, DONALD J.), 1996-1998 (Box R3386)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (COSTA BONINO, LUIS), 1994-1996 (Box R3386)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (CRASNARU, DANIELA) (CO-RESIDENT: SORKIN, ADAM J.), 1994-1999 (Box R3386)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (CROSSON, PIERRE R.), 1993-1994 (Box R3386)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (CRUISE O'BRIEN, DONAL BRIAN), 1993-1994 (Box R3386)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (CRUISE O'BRIEN, RITA), 1993-1994 (Box R3386)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (DANET, BRENDA), 1994-1995 (Box R3386)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (DAVIDOFF, FRANK), 1994-1996 (Box R3387)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (DE GRAZIA, MARGRETA), 1995-1996 (Box R3387)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (DENNIS, CARL), 1995-1996 (Box R3387)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (DE SILVA, KINGSLEY MUTHUMUNI), 1994-1995 (Box R3387)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (DE ZOETEN, GUSTAAF ADOLF), 1994-1995 (Box R3387)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (DHARMAPATNI, IDA AYU INDIRA) (CO-RESIDENT: FIRMAN, TOMMY), 1993-1996 (Box R3387)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (DICKSTEIN, LORE), 1992-1994 (Box R3387)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (DICKSTEIN, MORRIS), 1992-1994 (Box R3387)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (DIETZ, KLAUS)(CO-RESIDENT: HEESTERBEEK, HANS), 1993-1995 (Box R3387)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (DIOP, MOMAR-COUMBA) (DID NOT GO), 1995-1997 (Box R3387)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (DIXON, SUZANNE MARY), 1993-1995 (Box R3387)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (DOBSON, ANDREW) (CO-RESIDENT: REAL, LESLIE A.), 1995-1997 (Box R3387)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (DODD, WAYNE), 1994-1995 (Box R3387)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (DOHERTY, WILLIAM J.), 1993-1994 (Box R3387)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (DOTY, MARK A.), 1994-1996 (Box R3387)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (DOW, JOHN CHRISTOPHER RODERICK), 1990-1994 (Box R3387)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (DOWLING, LINDA), 1992-1995 (Box R3387)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (DUE, BODIL), 1993-1995 (Box R3387)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (DUE, OTTO STEEN), 1993-1994 (Box R3387)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (DUNN, STEPHEN E.) (CO-RESIDENT: DUNN, LOIS A.), 1995-1998 (Box R3387)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (DUNNING, JOHN H.), 1992-1993 (Box R3387)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (DU YAXIONG), 1995-1999 (Box R3387)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (DYBEK, STUART), 1995-1997 (Box R3387)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (DZIEWIECKA-BOKUN, LUDMILA), 1995-1998 (Box R3387)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (ECK, DIANA L.), 1994-1996 (Box R3387)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (EPSTEIN, LESLIE), 1993-1995 (Box R3387)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (ESCOT, POZZI), 1994-1999 (Box R3387)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (EYRE, LAWRENCE ALAN), 1993-1996 (Box R3388)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (FALWEY, LINDSAY) (CO-RESIDENT: FALVEY, JANICE), 1995-1996 (Box R3388)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (FEDERMAN, DANIEL DAVID), 1995-1996 (Box R3388)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (FEINTUCH, ROBERT), 1995-1996 (Box R3388)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (FELSTINER, JOHN) (CO-RESIDENT: FELSTINER, MARY LOWENTHAL), 1995-1996 (Box R3388)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (FINEBERG, HARVEY VERNON), 1995-1996 (Box R3388)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (FISHER, ROBERT M.), 1993-1998 (Box R3388)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (FLINT, ROLAND) (CO-RESIDENT: COWIE, HELEN ROSALIND), 1993-1999 (Box R3388)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (FLOYD, SAMUEL A.), 1994-1995 (Box R3388)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (FLUCK, WINFRIED), 1993-1995 (Box R3388)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (FOLBERG, JAY), 1995-1997 (Box R3388)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (FOMINA-COTIGNOLA, SILVIA), 1995-1997 (Box R3388)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (FOX, E. INMAN), 1994-1997 (Box R3388)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (FOX, ROBERT), 1994-1995 (Box R3388)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (FRAGA, EDWIN M.), 1994-1999 (Box R3388)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (FRIED, CHARLES) (DID NOT GO), 1993-1995 (Box R3388)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (FRIED, JOSHUA), 1995-1997 (Box R3388)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (FRIEDMAN, SY D.), 1993-1995 (Box R3388)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (FUCHS, DANIEL), 1994-1995 (Box R3388)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (GAISSER, JULIA HAIG), 1993-1994 (Box R3388)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (GAISSER, THOMAS K.), 1993-1994 (Box R3388)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (GALE, DAVID), 1993-1995 (Box R3388)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (GANA, AARON TSADO), 1994-1996 (Box R3388)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (GANOCZY, MARIA), 1994-1996 (Box R3388)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (GARDINER, JUDITH KEGAN), 1996-1997 (Box R3388)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (GASKI, HARALD)(CO-RESIDENTS: NORDSTROM, LARS G.)(SALISBURY-WENDT RALPH), 1994-1997 (Box R3388)
    - 120 SCHOLARS (GEORGIANNA, LINDA), 1993-1996 (Box R3388)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (GETCHES, DAVID H.), 1996-1997 (Box R3388)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS {GILBERT, JAMES B.), 1994-1995 (Box R3388)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (GILIOMEE, HERMANN BUHR), 1993-1994 (Box R3388)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (GIORDANO, JOSEPH) (CO-RESIDENT: GARINI-GIORDANO, MARY ANN), 1995-1996 (Box R3389)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (GIROUX, ROBERT), 1993-1995 (Box R3389)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (GLAZER, NATHAN), 1993-1997 (Box R3389)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (GOBBO, SIR JAMES AUGUSTINE), 1993-1995 (Box R3389)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (GODO, OLAV-RUNE) (CO-RESIDENT: WESPESTAD, VIDAR G.), 1995-1996 (Box R3389)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (GOLDBERG, HARVEY E.), 1993-1995 (Box R3389)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (GOLDSTEIN, ANN), 1994-1996 (Box R3389)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (GOLE, NILUFER AKAT), 1994-1995 (Box R3389)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (GONCZOL, KATALIN), 1993-1994 (Box R3389)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (GOONERATNE, YASMINE), 1993-1996 (Box R3389)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (GORMAN, ROBERT A.), 1993-1995 (Box R3389)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (GORMLEY, WILLIAM T.) (CO-RESIDENTS: WEIMER, DAVID LEO; SHARP, ROCHELLE; MANION, MELANIE F.), 1995-1999 (Box R3389)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (GOTTSCHILD, BRENDA DIXON), 1994-1997 (Box R3389)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (GOULD, WARWICK) (CO-RESIDENT: TOOMEY, DEIRDRE), 1993-1996 (Box R3389)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (GRAF, KARIN) (CO-RESIDENT: SARTORIUS, JOACHIM), 1993-1994 (Box R3389)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (GRAHAM, IAN), 1995-1997 (Box R3389)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (GRAY, STEPHEN R.), 1993-1994 (Box R3389)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (GREEN, J. RONALD), 1993-1994 (Box R3389)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (GREGORY, ANDRE) (DID NOT GO), 1996-1997 (Box R3389)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (GRENDROP, SILVIA C.) (CO-RESIDENT: LINDENBERG, CATHERINE STRACHAN), 1994-1996 (Box R3389)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (GROSS, ROBERT A.), 1993-1995 (Box R3389)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (GUBOGLO, MICHAEL), 1995-1996 (Box R3389)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (GUENNADIEV, ALEXANDER N.), 1995-1997 (Box R3389)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (HACKING, IAN), 1993-1995 (Box R3389)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (HALE, CHARLES A.), 1996-1999 (Box R3389)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (HALL, JACQUELYN DOWD) (CO-RESIDENT: KORSTAD, ROBERT), 1995-1997 (Box R3389)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (HALPERN, DIANE F.) (CO-RESIDENT: VOISKOUNSKY, ALEXANDER E.), 1994-1997 (Box R3389)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (HAMMOND, HARMONY), 1993-1994 (Box R3390)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (HANDURUKANDE, RATNA), 1995-1996 (Box R3390)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (HANSON, F. ALLEN), 1994-1995 (Box R3390)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (HARRIS, TRUDIER), 1992-1994 (Box R3390)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (HARTMAN, GEOFFREY) (CO-RESIDENT: WEISBERG, RICHARD), 1995-1997 (Box R3390)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (HASAN, ZOYA), 1994-1996 (Box R3390)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (HASHMI, ALAMGIR), 1993-1997 (Box R3390)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (HAYNES, JONATHAN), 1995-1998 (Box R3390)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (HELLER, THOMAS), 1995-1997 (Box R3390)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (HENDIN, HERBERT), 1993-1994 (Box R3390)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (HERWIG, HOLGER), 1994-1995 (Box R3390)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (HILL, NORBERT), 1994-1995 (Box R3390)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (HIRSCH, MARIANNE), 1994-1996 (Box R3390)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (HIRSCHFIELD, JANE), 1993-1999 (Box R3390)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (HOBAN, LILLIAN), 1995-1997 (Box R3390)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (HOLFORD, IAN), 1993-1994 (Box R3390)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (HOLLINGER, DAVID), 1994-1995 (Box R3390)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (HOLLINGSWORTH, ELLEN), 1993-1995 (Box R3390)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (HORNSTEIN, GAIL), 1993-1995 (Box R3390)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (HOUSTON, JAMES), 1994-1995 (Box R3390)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (HOUSTON, JEANNE), 1994-1995 (Box R3390)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (HOU WEIRUI), 1994-1995 (Box R3390)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (HOVDE, CARL), 1993-1995 (Box R3390)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (HOWARD, MILDRED), 1995-1997 (Box R3390)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (HOYLAND, DANIEL), 1995-1997 (Box R3390)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (HURD, HEIDI), 1996-1999 (Box R3390)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (IBRAHIM, JIBRIN), 1995-1996 (Box R3390)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (IDACHABA, FRANCIS SULEMANU), 1994-1996 (Box R3391)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (JAIDKA, MANJU), 1994-1998 (Box R3391)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (JAIN, MANJU), 1995-1996 (Box R3391)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (JASANOFF, SHEILA SEN), 1995-1996 (Box R3391)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (JENKYNS, RICHARD HENRY AUSTEN), 1994-1998 (Box R3391)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (JONES, ALEX S.) (CO-RESIDENT: TIFFT, SUSAN E.), 1993-1995 (Box R3391)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (JOSEPH, SARAH), 1993-1994 (Box R3391)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (KAMMEN, MICHAEL), 1994-1999 (Box R3391)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (KANSAKAR, TEJ RATNA), 1994-1995 (Box R3391)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (KAPUR, MALAVIKA), 1993-1998 (Box R3391)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (KARKLINS, RASMA), 1995-1996 (Box R3391)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (KAUFMAN, ROBERT R.), 1993-1996 (Box R3391)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (KAZEMI, FARHAD) (CO-RESIDENT: NORTON, AUGUSTUS RICHARD), 1993-1999 (Box R3391)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (KELLER, SUZANNE) (CO-RESIDENT: HAAR, CHARLES M.), 1994-1996 (Box R3391)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (KEYSSAR, HELENE), 1994-1996 (Box R3391)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (KHALIDI, RASHID I.), 1994-1995 (Box R3391)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (KIANDER, JAAKKO S.) (CO-RESIDENT: VARTIA, PENTTI LAURI ILMARI), 1994-1999 (Box R3391)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (KIRCHNER, MARY BETH), 1995-1997 (Box R3391)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (KIRK, STUART A.) (CO-RESIDENT: KUTCHINS, HERB), 1994-1996 (Box R3391)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (KLANICZAY, GABOR) (CO-RESIDENT: KOVENDY, MARIA), 1994-1996 (Box R3391)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (KLAUSNER, WILLIAM JAMES), 1995-1998 (Box R3391)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (KLEINER, JOHN), 1994-1995 (Box R3391)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (KNAUER, ELFRIEDE REGINA) (KEZIA), 1992-1996 (Box R3391)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (KOLLI, RAIMO), 1995-1996 (Box R3391)
- AC.2001.012: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1992-2000; AC.2001.012; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 record storage boxes
  - Bellagio Conference and Study Center, 120; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 record storage boxes
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (KOLVE, VERDEL A.), 1995-1998 (Box R3392)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (KOPELSON, KEVIN RICHARD), 1994-1996 (Box R3392)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (KOPROWSKI, HILARY) (CO-RESIDENT: OLDSTONE, MICHAEL BEAUREGUARD ALAN), 1993-1996 (Box R3392)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (KOSROF, WOSENE W.) (CO-RESIDENT: DIRUBBO, PATRICIA L.), 1995-1996 (Box R3392)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (KRAFT, WILLIAM) (CO-RESIDENT: KRAFT, JOAN HUANG), 1996-1998 (Box R3392)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (KRAMER, JONATHAN D.), 1993-1995 (Box R3392)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (KRELOWSKI, JACEK), 1993-1995 (Box R3392)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (KULASOORIYA, SABHARATNA ANANDA), 1995-1997 (Box R3392)